McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 3: Miscellaneous Materials, 1683-1988 December 19; 44 boxes; 9 folders; 6 items
  - 1896 Parade Sketches, 6 boxes
    - Austria: Hungarian Life Guard-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - United States of America: U.S. Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Sweden: King Oscar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - France: Cuirassier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - England: Scotch Footmen (seated), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Belgium: Lancer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Austria: Dragoon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Turkey: Lancer-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Turkey: The Sultan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Persia: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Persia: The Shah-Nasar-ed-diu (?), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Persia: Escort to the Shah, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Holland: Officer of the King's Ordinance, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Spain: Gendarme, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Austria: Dragoon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Austria: Emperor Francis Joseph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Sweden: Horse Guards, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - France: Cuirassier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Egypt: Arab, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - England: Scotch Footmen (seated), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - England: Postillion Royal State Livery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - France: President Carnot, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - China: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Spain: King's Sherbav (?), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Siam: Escort, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - France: Hussar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Egypt: The Khedive, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - United States of America: Navy, Infantry, Lincoln, Grant, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Germany: Emperor William II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Siam: Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - United States of America: "Uncle Sam," Navy, Infantry, Lincoln, Grant, Washington, Cavalry, Columbia, Heavy Artillery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - China: Group for top of wagon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Japan: Group for top of wagon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Souvenir Programs/Miscellaneous Magazines, 1902-1973; 1 box
    - Consists of approximately 28 souvenir programs from the Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey Circus (covering the years 1916, 1928, 1929, 1943-1946, 1951, 1954, 1955, 1957, 1959, 1961-1964, 1966, 1967, 1970-1973) and miscellaneous magazines and articles, including, 1 box (Box 81)
    - "Ringling's Magnificent Folly," Miami Herald, 1959 March 8; 1 box (Box 81)
    - Ringling Circus Museum Booklet, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 81)
    - 1942 July Esquire Article, 1 box (Box 81)
    - "The Strange Stories of Gargantua and Toto" Magazine, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 81)
    - Barnum Festival Souvenir Program, 1953; 1 box (Box 81)
    - "Barnum & Bailey 2 Hemispheres Bandwagon Program," Davenport, Iowa, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 81)
    - Variety Cover, 1972 January 5; 1 box (Box 81)
    - 1902, 1942 Route Books, 1 box (Box 81)
  - Artwork, 1988 December 19; 1 box
    - The New Yorker Drawing Print, Published 1988 December 19, By Shanahan. "Barnum & Bailey's Three Ring Binder", 1 box
      - 34 cm x 27 cm, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
      - 42.5 cm x 36 cm (in frame), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
    - Ink drawing of Horse, Signed Suba (?), dates not examined; 1 box
      - 29 cm x 35 cm, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
      - 36 cm x 39 cm (in frame), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
    - Drawing, signed J.M (appears drawn by a child). "Circus is Here", dates not examined; 1 box
      - Drawing, signed J.M (appears drawn by a child). "Circus is Here", undated; 1 box 30 cm x 23 cm (Box 82)
      - 34 cm x 29 cm (in frame), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
    - "General Tom Thumb" print, dates not examined; 1 box
      - 33 cm x 44 cm, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
      - 38 cm x 48 cm (in frame), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 82)
  - Scripts, Costume Designs, and Miscellaneous, 1889-1906; 1 box
    - "Montezuma, or The Conquest of Mexico" colored costume designs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Original Share List, 1899, Barnum and Bailey Ltd., 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 1905-1906 Financial Ledger, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - "1776: The American Revolution" Original Script, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "1776: The American Revolution" script and related lists, etc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "Moses" costume color plates, music score, prop lists, etc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers for the purchase of "Moses, or the Bondage of Egypt", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - "The Fall of Babylon" script and colored costume sheets, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Contracts with Order of Cincinnatus, 1889; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - "Montezuma" script, music, descriptions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous loose material, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)